var questionData = [
    {
        question: "1. Which of the following is a markup language used for structuring the content on web pages?",
        choices: ['a. CSS', 'b. JavaScript', 'c. HTML', 'd. PHP'],
        correctAnswer: c.HTML
    },

    {
        question: "2. Which CSS property is used to change the text color of an element?",
        choices: ['a. color', 'b. background-color', 'c. font - color', 'd. text - color'],
        Answer: a.color
    },

    {
        question: "3. Which of the following is NOT a valid CSS selector?",
        choices: ['a. .class-selector', 'b. #id - selector', 'c. $element - selector', 'd. element- selector'],
        Answer: "c. $element - selector"
    },

    {
        question: "4. Which of the following is NOT a JavaScript framework or library for front - end development?",
        choices: ['a) React', 'b) Angular', 'c) Bootstrap', 'd) jQuery'],
        Answer: "c. Bootstrap"
    },

    {
        question: "5. What is the purpose of CSS media queries?",
        choices: ['a. To include external CSS filesb', 'b. To apply different styles based on the device screen size', 'c. To add interactivity to web pages', 'd. To manipulate the DOM'],
        Answer: "b. To apply different styles based on the device screen size"
    },

    {
        question: "6. Which HTML tag is used to link an external CSS file to an HTML document?",
        choices: ['a. <link>', 'b. <style>', 'c. <script>', 'd. <css>'],
        Answer: "a. <link>"
    },

    {
        question: "7. Which CSS property is used to control the spacing between the content and border of an element?",
        choices: ['a. margin', 'b. padding', 'c. border', 'd. spacing'],
        Answer: "b. padding"
    },

    {
        question: "8. What does the acronym "SEO" stand for in web development?",
        choices: ['a. Search Engine Optimization', 'b. Secure External Object', 'c. Single-Page Application', 'd. Style Encapsulation Object']
        Answer: "a. Search Engine Optimization"
    }

    {
        question: "9. Which of the following is NOT a valid CSS display property value?",
        choices: ['a. block', 'b. inline', 'c. visible', 'd. flex'],
        Answer: "c. visible"
    }
    
    {
        question: "10. Which CSS unit of measurement is relative to the font size of the element?",
        choices: ['a. px', 'b. em', 'c. % (percentage)', 'd. rem'],
        Answer: "b. em"
    }
];